https://www.lagunaclay.com/privacypolicy

HomeClayGlazeMaterialsEquipmentToolsOrder NowResourcesDistributorContactMorePrivacy PolicyPLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICIES CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEB SITE.
Laguna Clay Company respects the privacy of every individual who visits our websites. This Privacy Policy outlines the information that Laguna Clay Company may collect and how we may use that informationPersonal DataLaguna Clay Company will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you (e.g., your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address ("personal data")) through our websites unless you have provided it to us voluntarily.
If you do provide us with personal data, we may use that information in the following ways, unless stated otherwise: we may store and process that information to better understand your needs and how we can further develop and improve our Laguna Clay Company services, offerings and products; we (or another party on our behalf) may use that information to contact you in this regard. We do not now and do not intend to sell, rent or market personal data about you to third parties.Information Placed Automatically on Your Computer - Cookies When you view one of our websites, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "Cookie" or similar file and can help us in many ways. For example, Cookies allow us to tailor a website to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.Privacy Policy
